# Hello, I'm Sophie

Frontend Designer, UI & UX, Content Creation, Digital Design

#### Contact

Sophie Feline Spang Kjeldsen 27/06/1997

Petersborgvej, 3a, 4tv 2100 Copenhagen

(+45) 42 33 03 29 sophiefeline@hotmail.com



**Portfolio** sophiespang.dk



**Pinterest** /sophiespang



LinkedIn /sophie-feline-spang-kjeldsen



Instagram @sophiespang



GitHub /soph8111



CodePen /sophiespang

I am an openminded 24 years old aspiring multimedia designer. I am a perfectionist who love to challenge myself.

I love to explore and challenge the universe of HTML, CSS and JavaScript but I'm also born with an aesthetic eye and enjoy making beautiful and playful things.



## SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, git and GitHub, REST API, CMS (Wordpress). NPM, Vite, SASS.

Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, XD, Photoshop, Premiere Pro.

## COURSES

Adobe InDesign, 2019

First Aid Course, 2015

Driver Licence B, 2014

### **EXPERIENCE**

2012 -

Le Management

Model

2020 - 2021

**Original Coffee** 

Cashier and barista

2014 - 2016

**Emmerys** 

Cashier and barista

2013 - 2014 Cafe Glad

Washing Dishes

## **EDUCATION**

2020 - 2022

Københavns Erhvervsakademi, KEA

Multimedia Designer (MMD), Frontend

2013 - 2016

**Aarhus Handels Gymnasium, HHX** 

IT A, Marketing/sales A, Marketing Communication C

2003 - 2013

N.J Fjordsgades Skole

Primary School, 0. - 9.